we
耶稣你是宝贵
你对我真宝贵
你留宝血洗净我
你爱使我自由
耶稣你是宝贵
你对我真宝贵
逆流宝血洗净我
你爱使我自由
我只想天天来赞美你
我只想要彰写你的名
主啊我爱你
我要更爱你
我只想一生来世逢你
我只想要荣耀你的命
主啊我爱你
我要更爱你
Jesus you are precious
you're worth it all to me
you share your breath it clings me
your love can set me free
day by day i want to praise your name
oh i want this manmagnify your name
lord i want to love you
i want to love you more
oh i want to serve you all my life
oh i want to glorify your name
oh lord i want to love you
i want to love you more
day by day i want to press your name
oh i want this man in five door name
oh lord i want to love you
i want to love you more
oh i want to serve you all my life
oh i want to glorify your name
oh lord i want to love you
i want to love you more
Jesus you are precious
you're worthy all to me
you'll share your pride to place me
your love can set me free
day by day i want to press your name
all i want is manify your name
oh lord i want to love you
i want to love you more
love you more
oh i want to serve you all my life
oh i want to glorify your name
olo i want to love you
i want to love you more
我只想天天来赞美你
我只想要彰显你的名
主啊我爱你
我要更爱你
我只想一生来世蜂蜜
我只想要荣耀你的名
主啊我爱你
我要更爱你
哦主啊我爱你
我要更爱你爱你
主啊我爱你
我要更爱你